Wow.
No, no, no, no, no.
The first I made you.
I am still seeing my idea.
I am still finding my line.
I amabolical.
Stop it's now.
From the beginning of the story, my
life is part of the cult in the moment.
We'll continue to walk through
the end of the last page.
End of the world?
In the last page.
Ola, ola, ola, ola!
Hear!
Let's rewind a little bit.
While Joseph and Avdol were battling
Mariah, Jotaro and Polnareff were.
And here's your drink, ma 'am.
A super-duper tall glass of whiskey
and soda on the rocks. Enjoy!
It looks delicious!
Oh, my, somebody's dying to quench
your thirst early this morning.
Scandalous.
Darling, how you do go on.
My husband's gone away on a business
trip and won't return for another week.
In that case, how about
enjoying a piece of cake?
Oh, don't trouble yourself, dear.
I'm quite all right.
Ha ha ha.
Kids are great, huh?
So innocent.
Hey, it's almost 9 a .m.
The old man and Avdol
are taking way too long.
They may have had a run-in with the enemy.
You think we should see
where they ran off to?
I guess.
Good grief.
It's time to go, Iggy.
Yeah, yeah, I know you're hungry.
You're not the only one. Believe me.
Hey, Iggy, where in the world
do you think you're going?
Geez, what a stupid mutt.
Let's go, huh?
Hey!
Make some room, would you?
I want to play, too.
No way we'd ever play with
a jerk like you. Oh, yeah?
You guys are the jerks of...
Oh, man, that really hurt.
Atta boy, you didn't shed a single tear.
That's impressive.
You sure you're okay?
So, kid, how old are you?
Four years old. Hmm?
Atta boy.
What about your daddy?
Where is he now?
Uh, he's at work.
I see, so your daddy's at work, is he?
Atta boy to you.
And where's your mommy?
She's at home doing laundry.
Atta boy.
So, you came here all by yourself? Mm-hmm.
Good!
Then there's no one around to stop me from
bashing your face and
for ruining my pants!
You gonna pay to get the mud cleaned off?
Or maybe you're gonna get a job
for the cash to pay me back?
Because you think I have years
to wait for some little punk!
to work his way through debt!
You little shit stain!
Mommy!
Joseph and Avdol are in the middle
of doing battle with Mariah.
So I, Alessi, shall take on the great
honor of killing Jotaro and Polnareff.
They're tenacious, to be sure, but I'll
do whatever it takes to achieve victory.
Atta boy, Alessi.
Enemies name, Alessi.
Stand, set.
God of storms and chaos.
Favorite phrase, atta boy.
Polnareff, keep your guard up.
Have you forgotten who you're talking to?
Hmm.
Seems Mr.
Joestar and Avdol already left.
And it doesn't really look
like there was a struggle.
Old man, Avdol, you hear?
Hey, Jotaro, I'm starting to
get a bad feeling about this.
Me too.
Oh, that looks yummy.
Come on, let me have a bite.
All right, just leave me some.
That docks with my sandwich! Hey!
Get back here this
instant, you mangy fleabag!
So you think I have nowhere to go?
You boys truly haven't
realized it yet, have you?
You only thought you were hunting me when,
really, I was luring you
here the entire time.
I'm afraid you're going
to fry this time, Joestar!
But you should run!
Hermit purple!
Adol might be able to defend himself
for now with his flames, but not you.
Time to die, Joestar!
The Goddess Bast is the perfect trap,
and it's also far more powerful
than your Hermit Purple!
Huh?
Oh dear, that's not good.
I dropped my change.
Now, where'd it go?
Not over here.
I'd lose my own head if it
wasn't attached to my shoulders.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
I can tell you're following us.
I can already see the evil in
your eyes, so don't lie. Got it?
I am so sorry, my good man.
Were you talking to me?
I'm not sure I understand
what you meant by evil eyes.
My loving non-evil parents
gave me these baby blues.
Well, what do you know?
It's the change I was looking for.
That so?
Then prove it.
It'll be easy to prove that
you're not a stand user.
Unless you really are one.
Conan!
Man, that was a close one.
So I was right, and you are a stand user.
He's running?
Hey, Jotaro! It's the enemy!
I'm hot on his trail!
Polnareff.
Polnareff, where did you go?
Over here, Jotaro!
Come back here, damn you!
Rage!
What the hell?
This guy's quick!
How can he be so fast?
Man, he's already so far ahead!
Huh? That's strange!
What happened to my voice?
What the heck is up with
my shoes they're ginormous.
Hey watch where you're going!
Don't you know running around in the
street like that can get you hurt
or worse you're lucky i wasn't the
front end of some out-of-control car!
Shut up idiot!
Why don't you go and lecture someone
else with that big mouth of yours?
Now out of my way i'm in the
middle of chasing someone!
Hey what do you think you're doing?
Let go of me!
What it's really high up here!
He's lifting me up with one arm!
Just how tall is this guy?
His face and hands are huge!
It's like he's a giant!
All right listen here
you pine-sized pissant!
I'm gonna teach you to
go around shooting your
ignorant little mouth
off to adults that way!
You think you're a big man just because
you're playing dress-up in adult clothes?
Annoying, good-for-nothing brat.
You bastard!
What the hell?
Move it, kid!
Get out of the way!
Wait a minute.
What the hell is going on here?
Why does everyone look like giants?
What?
What the?
Why am I a kid?
Is this really me?
I've been turned into a kid!
How is something like
this happening to me?
Could this really be happening to me?
There's no possible way
this kid could really be!
It could really be me!
Oh my god, this kid is me!
I turned into a little kid!
It must be his stance power.
That creeper must have found a way to put
a curse on me during our fight earlier.
I have a sneaking suspicion it happened
when his shadow stand lunged at me.
How did I let him do this to me?
Shit, this is bad, this is
really bad, what am I gonna do?
Joe! Joe,
uh, Joe, uh, Joe, uh, no, Jay,
Jackie, uh, what was his name?
I can't remember his name!
But I know this guy, he can help me!
So why can't I remember it?
Why can't I remember his name?
Hey there, little boy.
You, uh, didn't happen to see a
French guy come through here, did you?
This guy's about yay tall.
And he's got the exact
same haircut as you do.
Yeah, you're talking about me!
It's me!
Oh, good grief.
Asking a kid was an awful idea.
Huh?
Hey! Hold on!
I take it you've realized that your
body has been changed into a kid's.
Both your mind and your body
have regressed and soon you'll
lose all of the memories that
you've built up during adulthood.
You can't seriously be able to
erase everything I knew as an adult.
It's true.
It's all becoming a blur.
Guess it's about time, huh?
I love picking on the weak.
It's so amusing.
Atta boy Alessi, atta boy.
You're not getting away, you brat.
I can't say this too loudly, but picking
on the weak really gets me going.
Maybe too much.
I may be a bit sick in the head,
but hey, c 'est la vie, am I right?
It's like everyone says?
If you think you're a
little loony upstairs,
then there's a good chance
you're probably not.
It's my confirmation
that I'm totally sane.
And you can't imagine how good it feels
to know that I'll never lose to some kid.
Mister, whatever your
name is, you have to...
As you no doubt know,
my mission is to wipe
you and your good-for
-nothing cohorts from
the face of the planet.
Unfortunately, I don't
have time to savor the fun.
What do we have here?
Silver Chariot, eh?
I should have expected as much.
Seems you were able to
summon your stand as a kid.
But...
Just how strong is this stupid stand user?
Even Silver Chariot is a kid!
Mommy!
And he's just as weak as I am!
He bent a sword blocking those bullets!
My stand set reverted you
back to your childhood state?
Which means that all of your mental
abilities were reverted right along with you.
Your stand has gone back to a child stand,
the form it had before you two
were fully attuned to each other!
Do you get it now?
Good, it seems like you understand.
Atta boy, kid.
But, as weak as it is, your
stand is still at your disposal.
So I shall use my stand
for your execution.
Time to die, Polnareff!
You're mine!
Oh, no!
It broke in jail!
It hurts, doesn't it?
I meant to do that!
It hurts!
Little boy, are you all right?
He's gone.
So that guy runs for the hills as
soon as there's another adult around.
I'm safe for now, but that
freak was off his rocker.
Don't run off, little boy.
It looks like you're hurt. What happened?
Huh?
I, uh, well, the thing is, you see...
What are you mumbling about?
Those wounds need to be treated.
Why don't you come with me to my
house and I'll fix you up, okay?
Should I go?
If I don't defeat the stand user,
I won't turn back into an adult.
If the past is any indication, he
won't attack me with this lady around.
I can use that time to think of a plan.
Come on, hurry up. Whoa!
Oh, that's right.
You're hurt, so climb on my back,
but make sure you hang on tight.
She smells good.
This hurts like a bitch!
Damn that little crotch sniffer!
I'm not going to take this
from a snot-nosed kid.
He'll pay dearly for this.
I swear I'll butcher that brat!
From the looks of things, he
doesn't seem to be coming after me.
All right, little boy,
we're going to take a bath, so let's
take those clothes off, shall we?
You're completely covered in grime.
I'll clean those wounds up
and put some medicine on you.
What are you staring at, sweetie?
Take your clothes off.
Better yet, I'll take them off for you.
Here, raise your leg.
Hey, wait!
What are you doing, lady?
But what's wrong?
Nothing at all.
No, it is something.
It most definitely is something.
I don't know why,
but I get the feeling that I should
be really embarrassed about all this.
Wait, oh no.
What if my...
It's so small.
I don't know why, but for
some reason that makes me sad.
Hey, don't cry. Why?
After we get all that dirt off of
you, you'll be as good as new again.
Here, lift your leg.
I... I...
I'm so happy!
Are you positive it's okay
for me to touch you like this?
Of course it's okay, silly.
If we don't clean up those
wounds, they could get infected.
You've got dirt on your wee-wee too.
Oh, boy.
I can't explain why, but I'm
just so happy all of a sudden.
I guess it's all part of being a kid.
All right.
You be a good boy, okay?
Okay!
The fool's delirious.
Enjoy your stupor while you can, because
I'm going to chop your face in tow!
What could you be grinning
about, you silly boy?
Now, I think it's time
we wash your hair. Huh?
I hate using shampoo!
It gets into my eyes and I hate it!
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
Monkey, monkey, do!
Oh, I lost!
Alright, sit still!
Does it sting?
Yeah, it stings a lot.
Can you wash your hair
all by yourself? Uh-huh.
But not as good as you.
Oh, attaboy.
Yes!
That's the way, kiddo!
Atta boy!
That's impossible!
Thank you.
To be
continued...
I don't see that nice lady anywhere.
Come on, you that stupid?